// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is a judgement of the rightness or wrongness of something or someone, or of the usefulness of something or someone, based on comparison or other relativity",
    answer: "Value Judgement",
    options: [
      "Value Judgement",
      "Evaluation",
      "Comparison",
      "Venn diagram"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Is a piece of writing that takes a stance on an issue. It persuades the readers to support their claim or point of view.",
    answer: "Argumentative essay",
    options: [
      "Argumentative essay",
      "informative Essay",
      "Narrative Essay",
      "Descriptive Essay"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It introduces your topic. It informs your audience about the topic of your essay.",
    answer: "Introductory paragraph",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It is a one-sentence summary of your main point and claim.",
    answer: "The thesis statement",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " It comprises three or more paragraph that explains the reason why you support your thesis.",
    answer: "Body paragraphs",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question:"It’s a statement that presentIt restates your thesis and summarize all of the arguments made in your body paragraph.",
    answer: "Conclusion",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Problem that influences many citizens within a society.",
    answer: "social issue",
    options: [
      "environmental issue",
      "social issue",
      "international issue",
      "national issue"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It is a method or approach that is proven useful in listening to get information.",
    answer: "TQLR approach",
    options: [
      "Deductive approach",
      "Inductive approach",
      "Abductive approach",
      "TQLR approach"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "It means the quality of being based on valid reasons, good judgement or reasoning.",
    answer: "Soundness",
    options: [
      "Evidence",
      "Soundness",
      "Texts",
      "Reason"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How does the author help up believe his/her statement?",
    answer: "Evidence",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Evidence",
      "Reason",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What does the author want the reader to believe?",
    answer: "Claim",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Evidence",
      "Reason",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Is the supporting evidence strong enough to support the author’s main idea or beliefs?",
    answer: "Reason",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Evidence",
      "Reason",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "It is the characteristics of a sound reasoning Except:",
    answer: "Counterclaim",
    options: [
      "Quality of data",
      "Existenceof supporting details",
      "Counterclaim",
      "Relevance of addition data"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Is a statement that can be verified.",
    answer: "fact",
    options: [
      "Opinion",
      "Evidence",
      "Reasoning",
      "fact"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Is a view or judgement formed about something, not necessarily based on fact or knowledge.",
    answer: "Opinion",
    options: [
      "Opinion",
      "Evidence",
      "Reasoning",
      "Fact"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Is the capacity of producing desired output that can showcase a clear impression.",
    answer: "Efectiveness",
    options: [
      "Reading",
      "Speaking",
      "Output",
      "Efectiveness"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Refers to the condition or quality of being adequate or sufficient.",
    answer: "Sufficiency",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Refers to the conformity to truth or to a standard or model.",
    answer: "Accuracy",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Refers to the attractiveness or the state of wanting to know or learn about something or someone.",
    answer: "Appeal",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Refers to the facts provided or learned about something or someone.",
    answer: "Information",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];